http://www.gabar.org/privacypolicy.cfm

VIRTUAL LAW MUSEUM
The Virtual Museum of Law is an online extension of our physical Museum of Law, located on the third floor of the Bar's headquarters in Atlanta. Visitors to the Virtual Museum will find informational animated videos about famous Georgia and U.S. cases.
Visit the Museum
For Lawyers
arrow up
For Lawyers Overview
Member Benefits & Discounts
Membership FAQs
Become a Member
Fastcase
Attorney Resources
Succession Planning
FASTCASE LEGAL RESEARCH
Fastcase is a comprehensive national law library with online access to cases, statutes, regulations, court rules and Bar publications. Fastcase is ranked as one of the best member benefits the Bar offers.
GO TO FASTCASE
Our Programs
arrow up
Our Programs Overview
Committees
Sections
Board of Governors
Executive Committee
LAWYER ASSISTANCE PROGRAM
LAP is a confidential service outsourced to CorpCare Associates, Inc., to help State Bar members with life's difficulties. Members are entitled to six clinical sessions per calendar year.
MORE INFO
CLE
arrow up
CLE Overview
ICLE Courses
ICLE Course Types
Check Your CLE Status Report
Live Simulcast Locations
CCLC Forms & Fees
Webcasts for Self-Study CLE Credit
Webcasts are video recordings of live ICLE seminars. Choose the right course for your practice and earn self-study CLE credit anytime, anywhere you choose. View the list of available webcasts here.
Find a Webcast
Member Directory
member directory
Login
More ...
Member Directory
Advanced Search next slide
Search
Privacy Policy
Welcome to GABAR.ORG (the “Website”), a Website accessible free of charge to the general public with Internet access. The Website and its contents and related services are owned and administered by the State Bar of Georgia (“State Bar”).
By accessing and using the Website, or otherwise availing yourself of the services and information offered through the Website, “You” – the “User” – agree to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy is in effect at the time of each such access or other use of the Website.
You acknowledge that the State Bar may, from time to time, in its sole discretion and without notification to you, modify the Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to apprise yourself of any such revision or modifications each time you visit or use the Website. If you do not so agree, you are not authorized to access or use the Website in any manner, and you must exit the Website immediately.
I. SCOPE
This Privacy Policy does not apply to our Websites that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that have their own Privacy Policy or to information we may collect from you or about you in other ways, including through emails you may send to us.
II. INFORMATION THE BAR COLLECTS
A.  Membership Directory
The Website includes a Member Directory of attorneys who are licensed to practice law in Georgia. The Member Directory contains contact information, membership status, and public disciplinary history information. Attorneys may update their contact information from time to time. Members may elect to remove certain information from the Member Directory published on the Website by contacting the Membership Department or logging into “My Account” and changing their preferences.
B.  Website Account
Members of the State Bar may choose to create a Website account. Upon creation of an account, you may provide additional information to the State Bar. You are solely responsible for all use of the Website through your account and any information provided through such account. If you lose your password or suspect unauthorized use of your account, your must inform the State Bar immediately. The State Bar will not be liable for any loss or damage resulting from your failure to safeguard your password and account.
C.  Other Activities and Services
You may engage in other activities of the Website, or choose a service on the Website, where gathering personal information is necessary. Use of those services is entirely voluntary.
D.  Non-Personally Identifiable Data
During your visit to the Website, our servers automatically gather and store certain information about your use of the Website. This information does not personally identify you, and your e-mail address is not collected in this automatic process. Examples of the information that is automatically collected and stored includes: (i) your Internet domain and Internet Protocol address; (ii) the type of browser and operating system you used to access our Website; (iii) the date and time of your visit to our Website; (iv) the Web pages or services you accessed at this Website; (v) the IP address of the Website from which you came to this Website; and (vi) the Website to which you go when you leave this Website.
We use various technologies, including Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, to collect and store information when you visit the Website, and this may include one or more cookies, beacons, pixels, or other anonymous identifiers. We use this information to evaluate and improve the content of our Website and to make our Website more useful to our visitors. We also, use it to diagnose problems with our server, to keep our server running smoothly, and to learn about the number of visitors to our Website and the types of technology they use. If you wish to opt-out of the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, CLICK HERE.
E. Third Party Sites and Advertisers
The Website may contain links to third-party sites and advertisements from advertisers. The State Bar is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of those sites.
III. HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION
A.  Member Services
Personal information collected on this Website will be used for providing services to members.
B.  Financial Information
If you use the Website to make purchases, to register for events online, or to receive other services, the financial information collected by the State Bar during these transactions is used solely by the State Bar or third parties on behalf of the State Bar. This information is not shared with third parties except for the purposes of processing the transaction.
C. External Processing
We provide personal information to trusted third party businesses or persons to process such information for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
D.  Promotions
The State Bar may provide members’ contact information, excluding their e-mail address, to select outside entities so that State Bar members may receive information or promotional materials that may interest them. Members may opt out of receiving future offers by contacting the Membership Department or logging into “My Account” and changing their preferences.
E.  Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Data
We reserve the right to disclose non-personally identifiable data, including personal data aggregated in a manner that does indentify an individual, publicly without restriction, including to third parties who may help us provide or enhance the Website.
F.  As Required by Law, Good Faith, or Exigent Circumstances
The State Bar reserves the right to access, use, preserve, or disclose personal information as required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with the law or legal process served on the State Bar or the Website; (ii) protect and defend the rights, interests or property of the State Bar, its respective employees, marketing partners, agents or third parties; or (iii) to protect the personal safety of State Bar members or members of the public in general. Where applicable, the State Bar may also use information obtained on Website for the purpose of investigating and prosecuting attorney ethical violations or for other regulatory purposes.
Communications you send to the State Bar are not confidential or protected by any professional privilege or relationship and, if you send us a threat or message that describes or promotes unlawful activity, the State Bar reserves the right to share such threat or message with law enforcement authorities.
IV. CONTACT
Please direct all inquiries and other communications relating to the Privacy Policy to:
Visiting the Bar?
